(由TurboScribe轉錄。 升級到無限以移除此訊息。) So, the wedding caterers sent me this list
of 12 appetizers and I have to narrow
it down to six.
Food?
Give me.
So, did Monica tell you about this great
band called the Swing Kings that we're trying
to get to play for the wedding?
Since when are you into swing music?
Since forever.
I used to go all over town listening
to bands.
Chandler.
Gaff commercial.
So, did you book them?
Did you call?
I will.
Do you want me to call?
No, I'll do it.
You just stick to your job.
What is your job?
Staying out of the way.
This is impossible, Monica.
Why don't you just pick off 15?
There were only 12.
Oh, yeah, I added three.
What are peanut butter fingers?
I don't know.
Well, hello.
She's cute.
Should we go try to talk to her?
Sure.
It's one of the great things about being
engaged.
I'm not nervous talking to pretty girls anymore.
Could you guys help me?
Yeah, let me get that for you.
It's really heavy.
I got it.
So, hi, I'm Ross and this is my
friend Chandler.
I'm Kristen.
Kristen, hi.
Are you new to the area?
Because if you are, I'd love to show
you around sometime.
I actually just moved from four blocks over.
But this block is like a whole other
world.
Actually, it does have a very interesting history.
This street is the first street in the
city to have an underground sewer system.
Before that, sewage and waste would just flow
right down the street.
Sometimes ankle deep.
Smooth.
Excuse me?
Say, you're going to be starving after all
this moving.
What do you say I take you to
dinner tonight?
I'd like that.
Yeah?
Great.
Let me take this up for you.
After you.
Oh, no, no.
Oh my God!
Am I crazy or does this totally go?
Oh my God, you look so beautiful.
Thank you, Rachel, but look at Monica.
This is it.
This is the one.
I can't believe I found it.
Wow, you look so beautiful.
If I knew you, I'd cry.
Well, I'm Monica Geller, ball like a baby.
I'm Megan Bailey.
Have you found your dress yet?
Oh, no.
These dresses are all so amazing, but there
is no way I could afford one.
No, no, I can't afford this either.
No, I'm just here to figure out which
one I want.
Then I'm going to get it at Kleinman's,
this discount place in Brooklyn.
Day after tomorrow, they're having a huge sale.
Oh, thanks for the tip.
Yeah.
So when are you getting married?
Oh, I'm not.
I just like to try these on.
I do the same thing.
I'm just kidding.
I'm getting married July 25th.
I'm just kidding, too.
I'm getting married in December.
So when are you getting married?
Oh, May 15th.
Oh, it's getting close.
Yeah.
So who's your photographer?
Jeffrey.
We met with him.
Did he show you the photos of the
nude wedding he did?
The best man?
Wow.
I know.
I almost called off my wedding.
Oh, who's your band?
Oh, my fiancé wants the Swing Kings.
Oh, you're so lucky.
My fiancé wants the heavy metal band Carcass.
Oh, is that spelled with a C or
a K?
Oh my God, it doesn't matter.
They're both great.
Oh, you know what?
You know what?
Don't buy that here.
Now that you know what you want, you
should go to Kleinman's and you can get
it half off.
This place is so overpriced.
I own this store.
So, does this come in another color or...?
Hi.
Are you moving in or moving out?
Moving in.
Oh, can I give you a hand?
Oh, okay.
But, you know, be careful because the guy
who was helping me before had to leave
because he hurt his back.
Boyfriend?
No.
I'm Joey.
Hi.
Kristen.
Oh, wow.
What a beautiful name.
What is it again?
Kristen.
Ah, that's it.
Okay.
So, you live around here?
Yeah, yeah.
Right down there.
Listen, let me give you a little tip.
Do not take a nap on this stoop
or you could wake up with your shoes
gone.
I'll remember that.
Okay.
Hey, you know, listen.
Would you, uh...
Would you like to have dinner with me
tonight?
Oh, I have plans tonight.
Oh.
But how about tomorrow?
Sounds great.
Okay, all right.
Well, where does this go?
You look strong.
Why don't I take that and you grab
one of the boxes?
Okay.
Yeah.
It's taking so long.
I mean, forever.
Shit.
Come on.
So, this is Brooklyn.
All right, listen up.
There's usually only one dress in each size.
So, when they open those doors, fan out.
Now, this is what you're looking for.
Memorize it.
When you locate the dress, blow on these,
all right?
Three sharp blasts.
When you hear it, come running.
Got it.
All right.
Oh, they're pushing.
Don't be a baby.
Let's go.
Rachel, come on.
No, no, not it, not it, not it.
Don't crowd me.
This is it.
This is the dress.
Oh, my God, it's perfect.
I'm sorry, this one's taken.
Whoa.
Megan.
Monica.
You came.
Yeah.
This is my dress.
No.
Yes, it is.
You saw me wearing it.
And now you'll see me buying it.
What?
You freak.
You wouldn't even have known about this place
if it wasn't for me.
Look, you don't want to fight me.
Maybe I do.
I'm pretty feisty.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
Okay.
Hey, what do I do?
Did you find the dress?
No, you've got to get me out of
here, Phoebe.
These bargain shoppers are crazy.
You've got to get Monica.
You've got to hold my hand.
Oh, my God.
Excuse me.
Go, go, go.
Go.
So, Ross, how was your date the other
night?
Did you tell her about the magical ride
that starts with the flush of every toilet?
Laugh all you want, but she actually left
me a message saying she'd like to go
out again.
Huh.
In fact, I'm going to go call her
right now.
And I'll make sure to tell her my
friend Chandler says...
Hey, Jim.
Hey.
Listen, sorry I didn't stop by last night,
but I had a date.
Joe, when it's one o'clock in the
morning and you don't come by, that's okay.
Check it out.
It was with this really hot girl who
just moved in right across the street.
Really?
Right across the street?
Yeah.
When'd you meet her?
Two days ago.
Excellent.
You know, Ross met somebody, too.
What?
Hey.
Hi, how'd it go?
Oh, great.
We're going out again Saturday.
But I just found out she's also seeing
some other guy.
Really?
Joe, what would you do if you were
in Ross' situation?
Well, I sort of am.
I mean, yeah, I'm dating this girl who's
also seeing another guy, but I'm not too
worried about it.
Well, you shouldn't be.
Believe me, I wouldn't want to be the
guy who's up against you.
I mean, that doofus is going to lose.
So, this is nice.
I wish I didn't have to go.
Believe me.
But unfortunately, I have to.
Oh, by the way, what's the name of
the girl you're dating?
Kristen Leigh.
Bye.
Well, obviously only one of us can keep
dating her.
Obviously.
So how do we decide?
Well, now, let's look at this objectively.
I think I should date her.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Or, or I'm the one who dates her.
That's interesting.
But check this out.
I date her.
Yeah, yeah, I like that.
But just to go in another direction.
Okay, okay.
This can go on for a while.
Yeah, well, we should order some food, don't
we?
No, Joey.
Look, why don't, why don't we just let
her decide?
Okay?
Hey, hey, we'll each go out with her
one more time.
And, and we'll see who she likes best.
That sounds fair.
Maybe I'll take her to that new French
restaurant down the street.
Hey, wait a second now.
Look, we're going to have to set a
spending limit on the date.
I don't have the money to take her
to a fancy place like that.
Well, sorry.
That's what I do on dates.
All right.
Well, I guess I'll just have to do
what I do on dates.
So let's decide on a spending limit.
Yeah.
A slice.
Six dollars.
I was thinking more like a hundred.
Okay.
And I bought her 94 dollars.
Oh, I know.
Can you hand me a tissue?
You're out of Diet Coke.
Hello?
What?
You what?
Hey, you listen here, missy.
What?
That was that girl, Megan.
She booked the Swing Kings on the day
of our wedding and said I couldn't have
them back unless I gave her the dress.
Oh!
Does that mean carcass is available?
What am I going to do?
That is the dress.
Oh.
But Chandler wants the band.
I don't...
What do I do?
Well, just figure out a way to talk
him out of it.
How?
You're out of toilet paper!
Hey.
What's up?
I just wanted to come by and, you
know, wish you good luck on your date.
Oh, thanks.
Yeah.
What time are you meeting her?
We have 8 o'clock reservations at Gramercy
Bistro.
Well, that's in like 20 minutes.
You better get dressed.
I am dressed.
Oh.
Well, good.
For me.
What is this?
Did you give yourself a facial?
I have an oily T-zone.
Okay, dude.
Hey, you sent Kristen Flowers?
That's right.
You spent $100.
That's the limit.
You're screwed.
Actually, I sent the flowers before the actual
date.
So, technically...
Technically, I didn't break any rules.
Thanks for stopping by, though.
Oh, so that's the way it's gonna be,
huh?
Yeah, I can break the rules, too, you
know.
Oh, yeah?
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
Why am I not surprised?
You know what, Ross?
I'm not gonna let you get away with
this.
I don't think you have much choice.
Oh, we'll see.
Bye-bye.
Yeah, bye-bye.
Hey.
So, just a light layer?
Yeah, just...
Here and there.
Joey got meat sauce on the banister again.
Yeah, swing music is so out.
Phoebe, he's gotta be in the room for
that to work.
What are you guys talking about?
Well, um, we were just talking about the,
you know, the swing kings and just wondering
whether, you know, they were the right way
to go.
Yeah, I went to a wedding once where
they had swing music and, uh, two months
later, the couple got divorced.
And, no, I'm not saying that there's any
connection here, you know, but they did tell
me that's why they got divorced.
But I love swing music.
Yeah, but the swing kings, you know, they
suck so much that people actually die at
their concerts.
They just stop living.
All I know is when Monica and I
went to see them, we had fun and
there's another reason, too.
Well, what is the other reason?
I don't want to say.
Well, you have to because maybe it's stupid.
Well, it's just while Monica and I were
dancing to them, it was the first time
I knew that you were the woman that
I wanted to dance all my dances with.
Oh, crap.
So, they said our table will be ready
in just a few minutes.
Oh, great.
Is your back feeling better?
Oh, yeah, that's fine.
I guess the more muscles you have, the
more they can spasm out of control.
Kristen?
Joey!
Hi.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I like this place.
Yeah.
And you?
Technically.
I'm not breaking any rules, so...
Ross, this is Joey.
Joey?
Ross.
Hi.
It's nice to meet you.
I used to have a friend named Joey.
I don't anymore.
Our table will be ready in a couple
minutes, so...
Yeah, so...
Sure, I would love to wait with you
guys.
Thanks.
So, Joey, you look familiar.
Are you on TV or something?
Well, Joey doesn't like to talk about it,
but he's one of the stars of Days
of Our Lives.
That's right.
Don't you play a woman?
A woman in a man's body.
Much better.
So, you know, Ross, it's funny, because you
look familiar to me, too.
Have you ever been married?
Well, yes, yes, I have.
In fact, just the other day, Kristen and
I were talking about how I've been married
and how I have a son.
Yeah, little Eric.
That's right.
Wait, no, Ben.
So you've just been married the one time,
then?
Well, um...
You've been married twice?
Yes.
And...
another time after that.
Boy, I'm getting hungry.
Uh, hey, Joey, have you ever been so
hungry on a date that when the girl
goes to the bathroom, you ate some of
her food?
You said the waiter ate my crab cake.
Yeah.
So, uh, Ross, now, why did that first
marriage break up?
Hmm?
Was it because the woman was straight or
because she was a lesbian?
Do you two know each other?
No.
No, no, no.
It just seems like Ross is the kind
of guy who would marry a woman on
the verge of being a lesbian and then
push her over the edge.
Uh...
Wait a minute.
Were you on a poster for gonorrhea?
You ever slept in the same bed with
a monkey?
Hey, you leave Marcel out of this.
All right, you ever got stuck in a
pair of your own leather pants?
Hey, hey, have you ever locked yourself in
a TV cabinet, V.D. Boy?
Monkey lover!
Where do you think we lost her?
Probably around gonorrhea.
Geller, table of two.
You hungry?
There's a bear shit in the woods.
Hi, honey, I'm home.
Don't come in here.
Why?
Do you have another boyfriend in there or
something?
No.
We only mess around in his place.
You know, it's funny.
I started it, but now it's scaring me,
so could you come out here, please?
No, I'm wearing a wedding dress.
Oh, you got a wedding dress?
That's great.
Yeah, but I'm not keeping it.
Well, then why can't I see it?
Oh, I guess you can.
Okay, but I have to return it, so
you can't like it.
Okay, I promise I'll hate it.
Wow, you look hideous.
Really?
Yeah, that's like the most ugliest dress I've
ever seen.
Why do you have to return it?
Oh, because it doesn't really fit.
Oh, by the way, I booked the swing
kings.
Oh, that's great.
Great, thanks.
But that dress, I mean, it's like, ugh,
it's terrible.
It makes me want to just rip it
right off you.
Okay.
But you can't rip it.
Well, maybe a little.
Hey, guys.
You want to look at the song list
for the wedding?
Guys?
I thought you were going to be gone
all day.
All right, what's going on?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I should probably leave you girls alone.
Yeah, laugh all you want, but in ten
minutes, we're going to have younger looking skin.
You know, she could use a little.
I was going to say.
Hold on, hold on, hold on!